myjobhelper.com 2017-06-06

# MyJobHelper.com: Privacy Policy

* Thank you for visiting MyJobHelper.com (the "Site," "MyJobHelper.com), owned and operated by MyJobHelper.com. The Site is an Internet property of Surfin Mouse LLC. d/b/a MyJobHelper.com and its affiliated companies ("MyJobHelper.com ," "we" or "us"). This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") outlines the privacy practices associated with the Site. You agree to this Privacy Policy, in its entirety, when you: (a) access or use the Site; (b) agree to receive e-mail from us via the Site, or any other means; and/or (c) register on the Site to receive information from third party service providers.

**If you are a resident of the State of California and would like to opt-out from the disclosure of your personal information to any third party for marketing purposes, please e-mail us at privacy@MyJobHelper.com. Please be advised that where California residents opt-out from permitting their personal information to be shared, such individuals may still receive selected offers directly from us, in accordance with the law.  
**  
**EU and Swiss Safe Harbor**

MyJobHelper.com participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. MyJobHelper.com is committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries and Switzerland, in reliance on the Privacy Shield Framework, to the Framework’s applicable Principles. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield List. [<https://www.privacyshield.gov/list>]

MyJobHelper.com is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under the Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. MyJobHelper.com complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal data received **** or **** transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, MyJobHelper.com is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission.   In certain situations, MyJobHelper.com may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>. 

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website [[https://www.privacyshield.gov](https://www.privacyshield.gov/), you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

**Personally Identifiable Information Collected**

We collect your personally identifiable information when you sign up to receive job alerts. The types of personally identifiable information that we collect at the Site include, without limitation, your: (a) name; (b) e-mail address; and (c) phone number and postal address. In conjunction with our partner program, we also collect banking information and Social Security or Tax Identification number. 

**Use of Personally Identifiable Information**

By submitting your personal information on the Site, you agree that we may send a newsletter to you describing what types of job opportunities in your area. If you wish to opt out of the newsletter, please follow the unsubscribe directions in the email or you can contact us at privacy@MyJobHelper.com.

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We may also employ other companies and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf. Examples include sending direct and electronic mail, removing duplicate information from user lists, analyzing data and providing marketing analysis. The agents performing these limited functions on our behalf shall have access to our users' personal information as needed to perform their functions for us but we do not permit them to use your personal information for other purposes.

We will also use your personal information for customer service, to provide you with information that you may request and to customize your experience on the Site. We may also use your personal information for internal business purposes, such as analyzing and managing our business. We may use third parties to help us operate our business and the Site or to administer activities on our behalf.

_We partner with third parties that collect information across various channels, including offline and online, for purposes of delivering more relevant advertising to you.Our partners may link the personal information we share with them to the cookie stored on your browser or device, and they may collect information such as your IP address, browser or operating system type and version, and demographic or inferred-interest information_ _._

In certain situations, MyJobHelper.com may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. We also reserve the right to release current or past user information in the event that we believe that the user is (i) in violation of the Site's Terms and Conditions, this Privacy Policy or any other of our operating rules, policies, price schedules and other supplemental terms and conditions or documents that may be published by us from time to time; (ii) to commit unlawful acts; (iii) if such information is subpoenaed or requested pursuant to a judicial or regulatory proceeding or inquiry; (iv) when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others (v) if we are sold or acquired; and/or (vi) when we deem it necessary or appropriate including, without limitation, sharing your e-mail address with other third parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time to time, and Federal Trade Commission implementing regulations.

If MyJobHelper.com is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. If you do not want us to share your personal information with these companies, contact us at privacy@MyJobHelper.com. 

**Cookies and Tracking Technologies**

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by the Site and our partners, including marketing partners, affiliates, or analytics or service providers. _Our partners may link the personal information we share with them to the cookie stored on your browser or device, and they may collect information such as your IP address, browser or operating system type and version, and demographic or inferred-interest information._ These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. _In addition, our partners use this information to recognize you across different channels and platforms over time for advertising, analytics, attribution, and reporting purposes._ We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies to remember users' settings, advertisement targeting, and content customization. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

**Analytics / Log Files**

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data.

**Behavioral Targeting**

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by[clicking here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/)(or if located in the European Union[click here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)) Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.   
**Local Storage Object**

Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as Flash cookies or HTML5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5. To manage Flash cookies, please click here: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>

**Blog** Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at privacy@MyJobHelper.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

**Third Party Links**

The Website may contain links to other third-party owned and/or operated websites and, where you request information from Third Party Providers, MyJobHelper.com may transfer you directly to the websites of such Third Party Providers. MyJobHelper.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. In some cases, you may be required to provide certain information to register or complete a transaction at such website. These third-party websites have separate privacy and data collection practices and MyJobHelper.com has no responsibility or liability relating to them. We do not endorse, nor are we responsible for the accuracy of, the privacy policies and/or terms and conditions of such website. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit. These third party entities are independent third parties and are not affiliated with us. **Frames**

Some of our pages utilize framing techniques to serve content to/from our partners while preserving the look and feel of our website. Please be aware that you are providing your personal information to these third parties and not to Surfin Mouse LLC.

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**

Upon request MyJobHelper.com will provide you with information about whether we hold, or process on behalf of a third party, any of your personal information. If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, or delete it by making the change on our member information page or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

**Data Retention**

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. Please contact us if you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Social Media Features and Widgets**

Our web site includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and widgets, such as the ShareThis button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our web site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**Minors**

We do not knowingly collect information from minors under eighteen (18) years of age. No information should be submitted to, or posted at, the Site by individuals under eighteen (18) years of age. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children.

**Security**

All collected information is stored in a technically and physically secure environment. While we use reasonable, industry standard measures to protect personal information online and offline, no data transmission can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems. Access to this personal information is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public. All of our users' personal information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personal information. Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all MyJobHelper.com user personal information. Employees not adhering to our written firm policies are subject to disciplinary action. In compliance with applicable federal and state laws, we shall notify you and any applicable regulatory agencies in the event that we learn of an information security breach with respect to your personal information. You will be notified via e-mail in the event of such a breach. Please be advised that notice may be delayed in order to address the needs of law enforcement, determine the scope of network damage, and to engage in remedial measures.

**Changes to Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to change, modify, add and/or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Site. If we make any material changes we will notify you by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. Please check the Site periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the Site and/or acceptance of our e-mail communications following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of any and all changes.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions regarding this statement, or would like more information on our privacy practices, please contact us at privacy@MyJobHelper.com.

Surfin Mouse LLC. d/b/a MyJobHelper.com  
33 Irving Place FL3  
New York NY 10003

Notwithstanding anything else in this policy, we or a data provider we have engaged may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser to enable customized ads or content. The cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to data you have submitted to us, e.g., your email address, in hashed, non-human readable form. To opt-out of these cookies, please go to<http://www.aboutads.info/choices>.
